Guide to the Rice University Information Files, 1910-2019 UA 361
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Information Files
1910-2019
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 361
49.5 Linear Feet
The collection includes individual files for Rice related persons (faculty, students, alumni, staff, significant visitors), events, programs, traditions, campus artworks, organizations, buildings, and subjects. The formats include newsclippings, notes, correspondence, photographs, and other materials. The contents are donated by Rice community members and/or gathered by the Woodson Research Staff, and represent one of the most heavily used portions of the University Archives.
Biographical / Historical
The collection includes individual files for Rice related persons (faculty, students, alumni, staff, significant visitors), events, programs, traditions, campus artworks, organizations, buildings, and subjects. The formats include newsclippings, notes, correspondence, photographs, and other materials. The contents are donated by Rice community members and/or gathered by the Woodson Research Staff, and represent one of the most heavily used portions of the University Archives.
Scope and Contents
The collection includes individual files for Rice related persons (faculty, students, alumni, staff, significant visitors), events, programs, traditions, campus artworks, organizations, buildings, and subjects. The formats include newsclippings, notes, correspondence, photographs, and other materials. The contents are donated by Rice community members and/or gathered by the Woodson Research Staff, and represent one of the most heavily used portions of the University Archives.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research. Stored on-site at the Woodson Research Center.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges
Document Types
clippings (information artifacts); documents
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University; Rice University -- history.
- Series I: A
  - Aazhang, Behnaam
  - Abbey, George
  - Abdullah, King
  - Abedi, Mehdi
  - Abercrombie Chair
  - Abercrombie, Josephine E.
  - Abercrombie, J.S.
  - Abercrombie Lab
  - Abraham, Frank
  - [Office of] Academic Advising
  - Academic Awards
  - Academic Cup
  - Academic Development Plan
  - Academic Precedence
  - Academic Regalia
  - Academy of Texas
  - Accelerated Program, 1942
  - Accreditation
  - ACTER: Alliance for Creative Theater Education and Research
  - Action Learning Project
  - Adair, Linda
  - Adams, Dr. John A.S.
  - Administrative Career Training (ACT)
  - Administrative Computing Dept.
  - [Rice] Adminsitrative Officials
  - Admissions Office
  - ADVANCE (Advocating Diversity and the Need for Culture Exploration)
  - Advanced Placement Summer Institute
  - Adve, Sarita
  - [The] Advisor
  - Advisory Councils
  - Affirmative Action
    Related Materials
    See also: Equal Employment Opportunity
  - AGEP (Alliance of Graduate Education and the Professoriate Program)
  - AIChe
  - AIDS
  - Air Quality Management consortium
  - Air Terminal Museum
  - Ajayan Pulickel
  - Akers, William W.
  - Albee, Edward
  - Alborn, Ray
  - Albright, Madeleine
    See also: Baker Institute
  - Alcohol Policy Advisory Committee [APAC]
  - AlcoholEdu
  - Alcover, Madeleine
  - Aldrich, Virgil
  - Alexander, David
  - Alexander Von Humboldt Foundation
  - Alford, John R.
  - Alfven Hannes
  - Allen Center
  - Allen, Charles H.
    General
    See Nobel Prize Hoax
  - Allen, Herbert
    See also: Board [of Trustees, of Governors]
  - Alliance Francais
  - Alpha Rho Society
  - Alsobrook, Margaret "Sully"
  - Altenburg, Edgar
    See also: Browning, Loulin
  - Alumni Association (2 Folders)
  - Alumni Association - Travel
  - Alumni Calender
  - Alumni College
  - Alumni, Prominent (1920- )
  - Alumni Scrolls
  - Ambler, John S.
  - Americana Concept Program
  - American Association for State and Local History
  - American Astronomical Society Meeting
  - American College Public Relations Association
  - American Computer Experience
  - American Institute of Electrical Engineers
  - American Mathematical Society
  - American Physical Society
  - American Red Cross
  - American Society for Engineering Education
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineers
  - Americas Project
  - Amethyst Initiative
  - [Rice] Amnesty International Letter-Writing Table
  - Amorous Relationships
  - Anderson, Dr. Carl D.
  - Anderson-Clarke Center for Continuing Education
  - Anderson, Craig A.
  - Anderson, D. Kent
  - Anderson, Edward
  - [M.D.] Anderson Foundation
  - Anderson Hall
  - Anderson, Hugh R.
  - Anderson, John B.
  - Anderson, M.D.
  - Anderson, Ralph
  - Anderson, Wiley N., Jr.
  - Andrews, Florrie E.
  - Andrews, Forrest
  - Angel, John
    See also: Founder's Statue ("Willy's Statue")
  - Annan, Kofi
  - Annexstad, Kristine
  - Annual Fund Drive
  - Ansevin, Krystyna
  - Antarctic Expedition
    See also: Anderson, John B.
  - Anthropology, Department of
  - Aphorism
  - Apple, Max
  - Applied Physics
  - ALSEP - Apollo Lunar Surface Experiments Package
  - Arafat, Yasir
  - Arbuckle, Phillip
  - Archer, Bill
  - Archi-Arts (2 folders)
    Scope and Contents
    Folder 1: 1922-1946; Folder 2: 1947-
  - Architectural Society of Rice Institute
  - [Rice] Architecture
  - Arculus, Richard J.
  - Aresu, Bernard
  - Armed Forces Bowl
  - Armeniades, Constantine D.
  - Armstrong, Lance
  - [Agnes Cullen] Arnold Chair in Linguistics
  - Arnold, E.O
  - Arnold, June
  - Arrants, Edward
  - Arrowood, Charles Flinn
  - Art and Art History, Dept. of
    See also: Visual and Dramatic Arts, Dept. of
  - [Martel Center] Art Barn
  - Art - Campus
  - [Campus] Art - Outdoors
  - Art Car Parade
  - Art Lab
  - Artemis
  - Artificial Heart
  - Arts Rice 1972
  - Asia Society Texas Center
  - Asian Community Relations Project
  - Asian Studies
  - Asselin, Lydia
  - The Assembly
  - Association of Collegiate Schools of Architecture
  - Association of Research Libraries
  - [Rice] Astronauts
    Framed photos and mission patches in WRC display case - reception area
  - @ Rice
  - Athanasiou, Kyriacos
  - Athenian Owl Coin
  - Atherton, Jr. W. Clifford
  - Athletic Awards (Banquet)
  - Athletic Hall of Fame
  - Athletics - General
  - Athletics - General - Brochures
  - Athletics - General - Newsclips
  - Athletics - General - Reports
  - Athletics - Women
  - Atomic Research
  - Attwell, J. Evans
  - Aurora I
  - Austin, Joe Dan
  - Austin, Walter James Jr.
  - Austin's Original 300
  - Auston, David
  - Autistic Nursery
  - Autry Court
    See also: Gymnasium
  - Autry Family
    See also: Autry House; Autry Court
  - Autry Family - Endowed Chairs
  - Autry House
  - Autry House Auxilliary
  - Ave Lallemont, Hans
  - Awards and Prizes
    See also: [Rice] Service Awards
  - Axson Club
    See also: Control File for Axson Collection; Axson Collection attire and folder in oversize drawer info file marked Axson Collection Attire
  - Axson, Dr. Stockton
- Series II: B
  - Babikian, Virginia
  - Bacon, Thomas
  - Bado, Richard
  - Bailar, Benjamin F.
  - Bailiff, David
  - Baird, John H.
  - Baker 13
  - Baker, Adria
  - Baker, Burke
  - Baker Estate -- "The Oaks"
    Later MD Anderson Hospital Facility
  - Baker Family
  - [James A. III] Baker Hall
  - Baker, [Captain] James Addison
  - Baker, James A. III (2 folders)
  - Baker, Josiah Reynolds (Jay)
  - [Capt. J. A.] Baker Society
  - Baker, Stephen D.
  - Baker, Stewart A.
  - Bale, Red
  - Balfour, Alan
  - Ball, Zachary
  - Balloon Launch
  - [Rice] Balloon Study
  - Bally, A.W.
  - Baly E.C.C.
  - Bancroft, W.D.
  - Band (MOB)
  - Banks St. Apartments
  - BANNER Finance Systems
  - Baptist Student Ministry
  - Barak, Ehud
  - Baraniuk, Richard
  - Baring, Matthew
  - Barker, J.R.
  - Barker Texas History Center
  - Barnard Society
  - Barnea, Amir
  - Barnes, Joseph
  - Barnes, Mary W.
  - Barnes, Rodrigo
  - Barnes, Russell
  - Barnes, Susan
  - Barnes, Teveia
  - Barnett, E. William "Bill"
  - Barnett, Gregory
  - Barnstone, Gertrude
  - Barrera, Enrique
  - Barron, Andrew R.
  - Bartel, Bonnie
  - Barthelme, Donald (Architect)
  - Bartlett Aesthetics Program
  - Bartlett, Henry Leigh
  - Bartol, Kevin
  - Baseball, 1912 - 1920
  - Baseball, 1921 - 1930
  - Baseball, 1931 - 1940
  - Baseball, 1941 - 1950
  - Baseball, 1970 - 1979
  - Baseball, 1980 - 1985
  - Baseball, 1990's
  - Baseball, 2000's
  - Basketball n.d.
  - Basketball, 1914/15 - 1919/20
  - Basketball, 1920/21 - 1929/30
  - Basketball, 1930/31 - 1939/40
  - Basketball, 1940/41 - 1941/42
  - Basketball, 1942/43 - 1943/44
  - Basketball, 1944/45 - 1946/47
  - Basketball, 1950's
  - Basketball, 1960's
  - Basketball, 1970's
  - Basketball, 1980's
  - Basketball, 1990's
  - Basketball, 2000's
  - Basketball, Women's, 1980's - 1990's
  - Basketball, Women's, 2000's
  - Bass, P.M.
  - Bathroom Advertising Study
  - Batsell, Richard R.
  - Battista, Joseph
  - Baumgarten, Maurice "Dutch"
  - Bayazitoglu, Yildiz
  - Baylor College of Medicine
  - Bayou Startup Showcase
  - Beahan, Kermit
  - Bearden, Frank
  - Beauvoir, Simone de
  - Beckman, Dr. Herbert Karl Willi
  - Beckman Scholars Program
  - Beckwith, Boyd
  - Bedient, Philip
  - Beerman, Al
  - Beiersdorf, Herman aka Mickey Swift
    See also: TV
  - Belaunde, V.A.
  - Bell, H.L. "Tony"
  - Bell, Michael
  - Bell, Phillip
  - Bell, Robert
  - Bender Estate Gift
  - [Rice Institute] Benefit Plan
  - Benjamin, Don C.
  - Bennett, George
  - Bennett, John K.
  - Bennett, Sherry
  - Bennett, William E.
  - Bentley, Sarah
  - Benz, Julia
  - Beraud, Louise
  - Berkman, Lance
  - Berlin Wall section
  - Berndt, Jerry
  - Berry, Michael J.
  - Besen, Stanley M.
  - Bethe, Hans
  - Bevan, Jim
  - Bezos, Jeff
  - Bicentennial Commission
    See also: Vandiver, Frank E.
  - Biddy, Scott
  - Biden, Joe
  - Bielstein, Susan
  - Biesele, Megan
  - Bike Policy
  - Billups J. Edward
  - Binford, Neil
  - Biochemistry, Department of
    See also: Proposal for a Biochemistry-Chemistry Bldg LD 4711.R
  - BioE NEWS
  - Bioengineering, Department of
  - Bioengineering Medical Lab
  - Biology Building
  - Biology, Department of
  - BioScience Research Collaborative
    See also: Collaborative Research Center
  - Biosciences and Bioengineering, Institute of
  - Biosciences-Bioengineering Institute
  - [Rice University] Biotech & Healthcare Symposium
  - Biotechnology
  - Birch Anne
  - "The Bird"
  - Bird Roosting Research
  - Birkhoff, George D.
  - Bishop, Col. Raymond C.
  - Bixby, F. Lovell
  - Bixby, Robert
  - Bixel, Patricia Bellis
  - Blackburn, James B.
  - Black, Charles J
  - Black, Earl
  - Black Lab Theatre
  - Black Lives Matter Movement
  - Black, Matthew (Engineering alumnus), 1969
  - Black people at Rice
  - Black Student Association
  - Black Student Coalition
  - Black Students' 40th Anniversary on Campus 2007
  - Black Students Union
  - Blaffer, R.L.
  - Blair, Charles
  - Blair Madeleine Freeman
  - Blanchard, Frederic Thomas
  - Bland, R.L.
  - Bland-Hawthorn, Joss
  - Blanton, Ben
  - Blayney, Lindsey
  - Bloch, Felix
  - Bloomberg, Michael R.
  - Bloomgren, Mike
  - Blue, James
  - Bluebonnet Bowl
  - Board [of Trustees, of Governors] - Lists
  - Board [of Trustees, of Governors] - Historical
  - Board [of Trustees, of Governors] - Individual Member Information
    See also: Francis, W. H., Jr.; Parish, Alvis W.
  - Board [of Trustees, of Governors] - Newsclips, press releases
  - Bobb, Reverend Paul
  - Bochner, Salomon
  - Bohr, Neils H.
  - Boles, John B.
  - Bondos, Sarah
  - Boniuk Center for the Study and Advancement of Religious Tolerance
  - Bonn, George
  - Bonner Lab
  - Bonner, Tom Wilkerson
  - [Rice] Bookstore
  - [Rice] Boosters
  - Booth, H.S.
  - Boothe, Nancy
  - Bordeaux, Janice
  - Boterf, Chester A.
  - Boulanger, Nadia
  - Boulevard Service
  - Bourgeois, Andre
  - Bourland, Hardy
  - Bourne, Henry Jr.
  - Boutros-Ghali, Boutros
  - Bowen, H. Lee
  - Bowen, Ray Morris
  - Bowern, Claire
  - Bowling 1915/16
  - Boxing 1944/45
  - Boyd, Doug
  - Braam, Janet
  - Brace, Paul
  - Bracey, Claude
  - Bradley, Sen. Bill
  - Brady, David W.
  - Brady, Patrick
  - Braeswood (Houston neighborhood)
  - Bragga, Matt
  - Bramlett, Linda
  - Brams, Patricia
  - Brandt, Anthony
  - Brannon, Byron (Buster)
  - Bratter, Jenifer
  - Braun, Ben
  - Bray, Hubert E.
  - Breedin, Brent
  - Brelsford, John W.
  - Bremen-Rice Cooperative University (3 Folders)
    See also: Audio-Visual Box 32
  - [W.E.] Brice Colloquium Series
  - Bricks [for original campus buildings]
    See also: Rice Books; President Papers- Edgar Odell Lovett
  - Bridger, Grover Leon
  - Briggs, Faye
  - Brinkley, Douglas
  - Brisbine, Margaret
  - Briscoe, Birdsall
  - British Educational Mission
    See also: Shipley, Sir Arthur E.
  - Broch, Nathan
  - Broch, William R.
  - Brochstein, Susan & Raymond
  - Brochstein Pavilion
  - Brockman Hall for Physics
  - Brody, Baruch
  - Broker, Karin
  - Brothers, Dwight
  - Brotzen, Franz
  - Brown, Alice Pratt
  - Brown, Alice Pratt [Hall] (2 Folders)
  - Brown Art/Architecture/Music Library
  - Brown, Carrie
  - Brown Chair of Civil Engineering
  - Brown Family
  - Brown Foundation
  - Brown Foundation Gift of $5 Million
  - Brown, George R.
  - [George R.] Brown Hall (2)
  - Brown, Herman
  - [Herman] Brown Hall for Mathematical Sciences
  - Brown, James
  - Brown, Judith
  - Brown, Katherine Tsanoff
  - Brown, Lee P.
  - Brown, Peter Thomson
  - Brown, Richard
  - [George R.] Brown School of Engineering
  - [George R.] Brown School of Engineering Advisory Council
  - Brown Society
  - Brown Teaching Award
  - [George R.] Brown Tennis Complex
  - Brown, Watson
  - Browne, Frederic W.
  - Browning, Logan
  - Browning, Luolin
    See also: Altenberg, Edgar
  - Broyles, William
  - Bruce, Robert
  - Brunson, Emmett
    See also: Track Scrapbook (Section 1)
  - Bryan, Andrew Bonnell
  - Bryan Johnelle
  - Bryan Museum [i.e. Torch Energy, Visions of the West College]
  - Bryant, John
  - Bryant, R. L.
  - Bryson, Barbara White
  - [Andrew Hays] Buchanan Professorship
  - Buck, Carl
  - Buckley, Vince
  - Buckyball
  - Budget
  - Buffalo Bayou
  - Buffalo Bayou Brewery
  - Buffalo Soldiers Museum
  - Buildings and Grounds
  - [Campus] Buildings-Benefactors
  - Bulas, Casimir
  - Bull, John S.
  - Bullard, Daniel R.
  - [D.R.] Bullard-Welch Foundation Professor of Science
  - Bun, B (Freeman)
  - Burchfiel, B. Clark
  - Burgess, Kevin
  - Burke, Connie
  - Burnett, Sarah
  - Burns, John
  - Burrus, C. Sidney
  - Bursar
  - Burt, George
  - Busch, Arthur W.
  - Bush, George (former President George H. W.)
  - [George H.W.] Bush Presidential Library
  - [Rice] Business and Professional Women
  - [Rice] Business Club
  - Business Information Center (BIC)
  - [Campus] Business Manager
  - Butcher, Ernest Dell
  - [Dell] Butcher Hall
  - [E.D.] Butcher Professorship
  - Butler, Kellie Sims
  - Buy/Pay process department
  - Buyse, Leone
  - By-laws
  - Byrd, Alex
- Series III: C
  - Cabaniss, Weldon
  - [Louis] Calder Professor in Chemical Engineering
  - Caldwell, Robert G.
  - Calendar
  - Calendar of Events (Monthly)
  - Call to Conversation (President Leebron's)
  - Camacho, Zenaido
  - Camblin, Bob
  - Camden, Carroll
  - Camels in Texas
  - [Harry S.] Cameron Chair
  - Cameron Field
  - Cameron, Hugh Scott
  - Camfield, William A.
  - Campana, Joseph
  - Campanile (Tower)
  - Campanile (Yearbook)
  - Campanile Society
  - Campbell, J.I.
  - Campbell, James W.
  - Camp Logan
  - Campus Art Committee
  - Campus Crusade for Christ
  - Campus Pagans' Alliance
  - Campus Police
  - Campus Proposed Alternatives
  - Campus Site (original)
    See also: Photo Designated Area
  - Campus Tour
    See also: Morehead, James C., Jr.
  - Campus Water Well/Water Supply
  - Canant, Fred
  - [Senior] Canes
  - Cannady, William
  - Canning, Kathleen
  - Canterbury, Ruth
  - Canterbury Association
  - Cantor, Eric
  - Cantrell, Thomas
  - Capture Classroom Project
  - Career Services (2 Folders)
  - Caribbean Students Association
  - Carillon
    See also: Pomerat, Roland
  - Carlson, Edie
  - Carnahan, Norman F.
  - Carrington, Samuel M.
  - Carroll, Michael M.
  - Carson, Dan
  - Carter, Jimmy (former President)
  - Carvalho, Adolfo
  - Casbarian, John J.
  - Case, Lynn M.
  - Casteneda, James A.
  - Catalyst
  - Caudill, William
  - Cavallini, Maria Felicia
  - Cavanaugh, Kyle
  - Cavanaugh, Regina
  - Cavender, Kathryn
  - Cazamian, Louis
  - CelebrateART
  - Centennial Campaign
  - Centennial Celebration
  - Centennial Commission
  - Center for Academic Integrity
  - Center for African and African American Studies
  - Center for Biological and Environmental Nanotechnology (CBEN)
  - Center for Civic Engagement
  - Center for Collaborative Research
  - Center for College Readiness
  - Center for Computation Finance and Economic Systems (CoFES)
  - Center for Cultural Studies
  - Center for Education
  - Center for Electronic Texts and Images
  - Center for Energy and Environmental Research in the Human Sciences
  - Center for Ethics Medicine and Public Issues
  - Center for Excellence and Equity in Education (CEEE)
  - [Rice] Center for High Performance Software
  - [Rice] Center for the History of Leadership Institution (CHLI)
  - Center for Nanoscale Sciences and Technology (CNST)
    See also: Smalley Institute
  - [UH] Center for Public History
  - Center for Research in Social Change and Economic Development
  - Center for Research on Parallel Computation (CRPC)
  - Center for Scholarship and Information (CSI)
  - Center for Space Medicine
  - Center for the Study of Cultures
    See also: Humanities Research Center
  - Center for the Study of Languages
  - Center for the Study of Science and Technology
  - Center for the Study of Women, Gender, and Sexuality
  - [Shell] Center for Sustainability
  - Center for Teaching Excellence
  - [Rice] Center for Technology in Teaching and Learning (CTTL)
  - Center for Written, Oral, and Visual Communication (CWOVC)
  - Center of Quantum Materials
  - [Rice] Center on Race, Religions, and Urban Life (CORRUL)
  - Century Scholars program
  - Chae, Suchan
  - [Rice] Chamber Orchestra
  - Chamberlain, Joseph W.
  - Chance, Jane
  - Chandler, Asa C.
  - Chaney, Clayton [DJ Chaney]
  - Chang, Yung-Ho
  - Chao Center for Asian Studies
  - Chapel
    See also: [Rice] Memorial Chapel
  - Chapman, Alan
  - Chapman, Richard
  - Chapman, Walter
  - Characklis, William
  - Charter
  - Charter Society
  - Charyn, Jerome
  - Chavanne, Harry Joseph
  - [Harry and Hazel] Chavanne Chair in Religious Studies
  - Cheatham, John B.
  - Cheerleaders
  - Chemical and Biomolecular Engineering
  - Chemical Engineering, Department of
  - Chemical Society
  - Chemistry Building and Laboratory
    see also: Keck Hall
  - Chemistry, Department of
  - Chen, Shih-Hui
  - Cherry, Emma Richardson
  - [Rice] Chess club
  - [Rice] Child care
  - Chillman, James Jr.
  - [Rice] Chinese Alumni/Student Association
  - Chinese Christian Fellowship
  - Chinese Language Teaching, Institute of
  - [Rice] Chorale
  - Christ Church Cathedral
  - Cite
  - "CITI" Computer and Information Technology Institute
  - Citron, Marcia
  - Ciufolini, Marco A.
  - Civic Duty Rice
  - Civil & Environmental Engineering (3 Folders)
  - Civinet
  - Clark, Howard C.
  - Clark, James A.
    See also: Energy Research and Education Foundation
  - Clark, John W.
  - Clark, Ramsey
  - Clark, Susan L.
  - Clarke, Robert
  - Clarkson, Gavin
  - Classical Studies, Dept. of
  - Classroom Building (Proposal)
  - Clayton, Donald D.
  - Clayton Genealogy library
  - Cleanology
  - Cleveland, Alexander S.
  - Cleveland-Lovett Literary Society (CLLS)
  - [Alan and Gladys] Cline Chair in Economics and Finance
  - Cline, Gladys
  - Clinton, Former President Bill
  - Cloutier, Paul
  - Club Asia
  - Club 13
  - [Rice] Coaches
  - Cobb, Trevor
  - Cochran, Barbara G.
  - Code of Judicial Procedure
    See also: [Code of] Judicial Procedure
  - Code of Student Conduct
  - Co-ed Colleges
  - [Rice] Coffee House
  - Coffin, William S
  - Cohen, George and Esther
  - Coherent Minor
  - Cohn, Arthur Benjamin
    See also: A/V materials for video of historical marker, dedication ceremony 1986
  - Cohn House
  - Colbert, Daniel
  - Coleman, Jim
  - Collaborative Research Center
    See also: Bioscience Research Collaborative
  - [Rice Institute] Collection of Fishes
  - College Assistance Peer Program (CAPP)
  - College Career Program
  - College Cheers
  - College Court
  - [Rice] College Masters
  - College System
    See also: Residential Colleges System
  - College Teachers of English of Texas
  - College Women's Club of Houston
  - Collegiate Churchmen
    See also: Canterbury Association
  - Collins, Katherine E.
  - [Rice] Colors
  - Colvin, Vicki
  - Commencement - General
  - Commencement Speakers at Rice University
    1926: Ames, Joseph Sweeton; Barnston, Henry Rabbi; 1928: Finley, John Huston; 1930: Angell, John; Dickinson, Pauline Martin; 1932: Buttrick, George A.; 1935: Budd, Ralph; 1937: Graves, Frank P.; 1938: Ashe, Samuel S.; Davidson, Edward; 1940: Angell, James R.; 1941: Bowman, Isiah; 1947: Bender, Eugene L.; Fisher, Wilton M.; 1956: Van Vleck, Dr. J.H.; 1958: Follies; 1969: Blau, Joseph L.
  - Commerce, Department of
  - Commission on Women
    See also: [Rice] Women's Commission
  - [Rice] Committees
  - Committee Service
  - "The Communicator"
  - [Rice] Community Garden
  - [Rice] Community Involvement Center
  - Composting Pilot Project
  - Compton, Arthur H.
  - Comptroller's Dept.
  - [Dept. of] Computational and Applied Mathematics
  - Computational Engineering
  - Computer Planning Board
  - Computer Science Camp
  - Computer Science, Dept. of (4 Folders)
  - Computing at Rice
  - Computing, Blue Ribbon Panel on
  - [Rice] Computing Team
  - Conant, James Bryant
  - Conant, Ralph W.
  - Condon, William Joseph
  - Conference for African-American Researchers in the Mathematical Sciences
  - Conference USA (CUSA)
  - Congressional Club
  - Conklin, E.G.
  - Connally, John B.
  - The Connection
  - Connelly, Brian
  - Connexions
  - Conover, Al
  - Controller's Office
  - Convocations
  - Cook, David
  - Cook, Raymond and Florence
  - Cooke, Nancy
  - Cooper, Christiane Ebert
  - Cooper, Jen
  - Cooper, Joseph
  - Cooper, Keith D.
  - Cooper, Paul
  - Cooperative Store
  - [Rice University] Coordinates
  - Copeland, James E.
  - Corcoran, Marjorie
  - Corey, E.J.
  - Cornwell, John
  - Coronavirus
  - Corporate and Foundation Relations, Office of
  - Corporate Associates Seminar
  - Cosby, Bill
  - Costello, Kathryn R.
  - Cotner, Robert Crawford
  - Cotton Bowl
  - Course Evaluations
  - Coursera
  - Courses, New - Approval
  - Courtlandt Place
  - Coury, Anny (sculptor of white marble owl)
  - Cousins, Bill
  - Cowan, Finis E.
  - Cowan, Ken
  - Cox, Alan
  - Cox, Edward
  - Cox, John L.
  - [J. W.] Cox Laboratory for Biomedical Engineering
  - Cox, Steven J.
  - Craig, Hardin, Jr. (+Mrs.)
  - Craig, Hardin, Sr.
  - Cram, Goodhue and Ferguson Exhibit
  - Cram, Ralph Adams
  - Crane, David A.
  - Cranmer Club
  - Crawford, Sarah N.
  - Creekmore, J. Howard
  - Crist, Lynda
  - Criswell, James
  - "The Critic"
  - Croneis, Carey
  - Cronin, Justin
  - Cronin, Mary
  - Cross Country
  - Crouse, Wayne
  - Crowell, Steven G.
  - Crownover, James W.
  - Cruikshank, Robert
  - Cruikshank, Thomas H.
  - Cruz Jose Jr.
  - Cullen Family
  - [Craig Francis] Cullinan Chair of Architecture
  - Cullinan, J. S.
    See also: Shadyside
  - Cummings, Robert E.
  - Curl, Robert
  - Curral, Steve
  - Curriculum Changes
  - Currie, Dean
  - Curtis, Doris M.
  - Curtis, Morton L.
  - Cuthbertson, Gilbert
  - [Rice] Cycling Team
- Series IV: D
  - DaCamara, Harry Shirley